Guide to the Lahiton - Cinema World image archive M2036
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 10: Theater
  - Sub-series 1: Actors
    - Wilentz, Dallek (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Yadin, Yosef (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Yakir, Avi (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Yitshaki, Aliza (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Zarai, Shafrira (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Sub-series 2: Performances
    Images from live theater performances
    - "Aladin" אלאדין (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - "Allah karim" אללה קארים (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - "Al tirdu mi-meni" אל תרדו ממני (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - "Avraham ehad" אברהם אחד (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - "Be-mazal betulah" במזל בטולה (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - "Bunker" בונקר (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - "Gevirati ha-naah" גבירתי הנעה (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - "Hafatsim" חפצים (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - "Ha-nitsol" הניצול (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - "Hataim" חטאים (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - "Havat ha-hayot" חוות החיות (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - "Kanar al ha-gag" כנר על הגג (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - "Likhlukhit" לכלוכית (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - "Malkat ha-kitah" מלכת הכיתה (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - "Nisim ve-niflaot bi-kufsot shimurim" נסים ונפלאות בקופסות שימורים (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - "Rak shalosh ve-lalekhet" רק שלוש וללכת (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - "Sipur ha-hipushiyot" סיפור החיפושיות (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - "Tsehokim sheka-eleh" צחוקים שכאלה (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - "Uncle Vanya" (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - "Yetush ba-rosh" יתוש בראש (Box 83, Folder 23)
- Series 11: Unsorted images
  Images, many of which also appear in the sorted categories, that were deemed too numerous and time consuming to arrange
  - Miscellaneous images (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
  - Miscellaneous images (Box 85, Folder 1-4)
  - Miscellaneous images (Box 86, Folder 1-4)
  - Miscellaneous images (Box 87, Folder 1-6)
  - Miscellaneous images (Box 88, Folder 1-5)
  - Miscellaneous materials (Box 89, Folder 1-5)
  - Oversize photos (Flatbox-small 90)